<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>EYC Team Race Blog</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/eyctr/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/eyctr/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 22:41:19 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 22:41:19 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Team Racing for Dummies - and for Experienced Sailors Too!!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never raced? Never team raced? Come play with us!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images%5C2018-07-09_12h10_48.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;image featured&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/eyctr/images/2018-07-09_12h10_48.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
EYC has three J22 that are sailing every other Monday, practicing team racing and periodically scrimmaging with neighboring yacht clubs. Come join us to learn the game, learn racing rules and especially learn to sail fast. Things you can take back to your fleet racing and cruising.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Open to EYC members and their non-member friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;image featured&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/eyctr/images/2018-07-09_12h11_10.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 05:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/eyctr/info/2018/07/10/teamrace-basics.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/eyctr/info/2018/07/10/teamrace-basics.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>info</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AYC 3-2-1 Regatta Update</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The 3-2-1- event is rapidly approaching and it’s gonna be amazing!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is the schedule that we need to follow to have success:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;(MON) May 14&lt;/b&gt; -  Everyone must come to the Team Race practice to get ourselves dialed in.&lt;br /&gt;
There will be 3x J22s to sail, with alternates switching in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are working to arrange setting foot on one of the EYC J30s (not sailing just familiarizing with strings etc).  If anyone personally knows an owner it would be appreciated if you ask for this quick favor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boat maintenance to follow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WED/ THUR 16/17&lt;/b&gt; - Please get out there and sail.  I’ll be going out Thursday with some of you and hope to have the other 2x boats filled also. Reserve the boats by calling EYC and speaking to Nan Walker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;SAT 19&lt;/b&gt; -  We need to splash the 3 boats and take them around to AYC (berthing confirmed).  With the Viper event at EYC it is gonna be chocker blocked.  Let’s assume this needs to happen midday while they are out racing and completed before they return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUNDAY MAY 20&lt;/b&gt; - We go have fun, get dialed in on this “test run” event, and kick some butts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here for all questions!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Logan Hearn #2605
513.324.3447 primary
443.254.3671&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 10:36:23 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/eyctr/regatta/2018/05/10/regatta-update-321.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/eyctr/regatta/2018/05/10/regatta-update-321.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>regatta</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hinman Masters 2018- We need players!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;image featured&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/eyctr/images/nyycTR_hinman.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Greetings fellow EYCers – summer is here and it’s time to start planning for the Hinman Masters again. The regatta is Friday – Sunday, August 18-20. Thanks for the club for sponsoring us for this event again this and helping us grow team racing at EYC.  We are working on solidifying the team and I need to firm up who will be sailing. If you are interested and able to sail, please let me know your interest level –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Yes James, I am 100% committed to sailing, thanks for asking me!&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Yes James, I am very interested and can say with a 75% certainty I will sail.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Yes, James I am interested, but really can’t commit for sure at this point.&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to another great regatta!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Appel - jamesappel@icloud.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 04:13:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/eyctr/regatta/2018/05/10/hinman-roster-ask.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/eyctr/regatta/2018/05/10/hinman-roster-ask.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>regatta</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Team Racing Involvement!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;image featured&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/eyctr/images/ohare_usyru_1986.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;I am excited for team racing at EYC and at regatta challenges this season. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been involved with team racing since my home club San Francisco YC hosted the US Sailing championship in 1986!  (see pic attached) Nowawdays, I don’t get to team race or practice very often so I am hoping you all will join me in EYC’s J22’s locally and at regattas we get invited to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I plan to contribute as a team member but also support with my educational focus on the tactics and strategy of team racing.
A lot of good info in this &lt;a href=&quot;http://slideplayer.com/slide/7000515/&quot;&gt;slideshow &lt;/a&gt; posted by my friend Steve Hunt:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you on the water.  We have a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.signupgenius.com/go/10c0a4cadac28a2fa7-practice&quot;&gt;sign up genius page&lt;/a&gt; to maintain a list of who plans to sail each night.  Please update it!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 17:36:23 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/eyctr/info/2018/05/09/ohare-involvement.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/eyctr/info/2018/05/09/ohare-involvement.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>info</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Make Mine A Double is at it again.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The 2018 Etchells racing season has begun, and two thirds of the Make Mine A Double (aka MMAD) team is a part of the EYC team race team. The great part about that is that we can bring the communications from our boat to the team race team - and vice versa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since we swap roles, I get a better chance to observe Reid’s starting tactics, and he gets a chance to hear the communications I give during the sequence. And we all learn a lot about boat-boat tactics. The disciplines of team and match racing rely on rules knowledge and boat to boat tactics to make successful competitors. There is a significant trickle down to fleet racing - you can break a fleet race into a bunch of little match races, and throw some team races moves in too. who hasn’t had to slow down a sailor in the last race to try to allow a competitor to get between them so you can move up in the standings?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ever got taken out at a mark because someone else knew the rules better? Team racing will begin to teach those rules as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the other piece you get with these disciplines is boat handling. The races are really short, and precise boat handling will get you extra feet of advantage in a game where inches count.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, if you have ever thought about it, now is the time to join. The EYC team race team is growing, while we don’t go to too many events, it isn’t for a lack of wanting to, it is for a lack of team members. We need more team members so we can fill out more teams to go places. We have at least 5 solid invitations this year that we will have to turn down, because we just don’t have the people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;C’mon out and join the team for some practices, see if it’s your gig. No experience necessary! I guarantee it will help your everyday fleet racing - even if you only race Wednesdays or Fridays!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 13:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/eyctr/regatta/2018/05/08/mmad-update.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/eyctr/regatta/2018/05/08/mmad-update.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>regatta</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>EYC Team Race Members in the House at NOOD!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;image featured&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/eyctr/images/hellyhansen_nood_2018.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had many of our team race members participating in the Annapolis NOOD this weekend including the following&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jeff Borland - Etchells&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
Reid McLaughlin - Etchells&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
Carl Smit - Viper&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
Dean Balcirak - Viper&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
Susie Balcirak - Viper&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
David Malkin - J22&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Others I am sure I was not aware of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Way to represent EYC Team Racers!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 05:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/eyctr/regatta/2018/05/04/eyctr-in-the-house.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/eyctr/regatta/2018/05/04/eyctr-in-the-house.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>regatta</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We gotta pay to play</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;image featured&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/eyctr/images/j22.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EYC is supporting us, we have to support them - for many reasons. We get to use the J-22s, we have Nan supporting us, and the support of the board. We need to show that we appreciate it. There are also insurance things to consider.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, we ALL need to sign up as pay the nominal fees and sign the waiver to be a part of the team. Both Skippers AND Crew.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Skippers - $250 plus deposit (a hold on a CC)
Crew - $100&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;* For just a bit more, you can also get access to the club’s fleet of kayaks, SUPs, etc - and access to the J-22s on days other than Monday or Tuesday **&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We expect 100% participation!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Click the link - EYC Watercraft Access Program - It’s quick and easy. Contact Nan Walker with any questions - waterfront@eastportyc.org&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 10:36:23 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/eyctr/info/2018/04/29/pay-fee.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/eyctr/info/2018/04/29/pay-fee.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>info</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AYC 3-2-1 Regatta - May 20 - We need players!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;image featured&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/eyctr/images/eyctr-400.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our first event of the season! This is a one day regatta hosted by AYC, but using the EYC boats as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This event has three formats rolled into a one day event, 3 on 3 team racing, 2 on 2 team racing, and match racing. What a great way to experience all the disciplines!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All you need to do is to be able to crew a j-22. we’ve got some experienced types that will be driving, we need 3 or 4 more people to round out the team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contact Logan Hearn - loghearn@gmail.com - 443.254.3671 to sign up, or ask questions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 10:36:23 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/eyctr/regatta/2018/04/28/first-practice.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/eyctr/regatta/2018/04/28/first-practice.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>regatta</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Practice is on!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;image featured&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/eycteam_2018.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Practice is on! First night is Monday, April 30!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All skippers and crews - we have boats ready to sail, and we need bodies!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you plan to be a t practice Monday night, respond to this email or text 410-320-1843 with your name, email address and cell number If we get enough people, we will have a practice and then some fun talking about it afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We need RSVPs to make sure we have enough people to warrant splashing the boats.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 10:36:23 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/eyctr/first-post.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/eyctr/first-post.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>practice</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
