<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>EYC Team Race Blog</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>https://reidmclaughlin.github.io/eyctr/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://reidmclaughlin.github.io/eyctr/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 13:53:13 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 13:53:13 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>We gotta pay to play</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;image featured&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pic03.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EYC is supporting us, we have to support them - for many reasons. We get to use the J-22s, we have Nan supporting us, and the support of the board. We need to show that we appreciate it. There are also insurance things to consider.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, we ALL need to sign up as pay the nominal fees and sign the waiver to be a part of the team. Both Skippers AND Crew.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Skippers - $250 plus deposit (a hold on a CC)
Crew - $100&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;* For just a bit more, you can also get access to the club’s fleet of kayaks, SUPs, etc - and access to the J-22s on days other than Monday or Tuesday **&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We expect 100% participation!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Click the link - EYC Watercraft Access Program - It’s quick and easy. Contact Nan Walker with any questions - waterfront@eastportyc.org&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 10:36:23 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://reidmclaughlin.github.io/eyctr/2018/04/29/pay-fee.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://reidmclaughlin.github.io/eyctr/2018/04/29/pay-fee.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AYC 3-2-1 Regatta - May 20 - We need players!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;image featured&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/eyctr-400.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our first event of the season! This is a one day regatta hosted by AYC, but using the EYC boats as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This event has three formats rolled into a one day event, 3 on 3 team racing, 2 on 2 team racing, and match racing. What a great way to experience all the disciplines!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All you need to do is to be able to crew a j-22. we’ve got some experienced types that will be driving, we need 3 or 4 more people to round out the team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contact Logan Hearn - loghearn@gmail.com - 443.254.3671 to sign up, or ask questions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 10:36:23 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://reidmclaughlin.github.io/eyctr/regatta/2018/04/28/first-practice.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://reidmclaughlin.github.io/eyctr/regatta/2018/04/28/first-practice.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>regatta</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Practice is on!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;image featured&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pic02.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Practice is on! First night is Monday, April 30!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All skippers and crews - we have boats ready to sail, and we need bodies!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you plan to be a t practice Monday night, respond to this email or text 410-320-1843 with your name, email address and cell number If we get enough people, we will have a practice and then some fun talking about it afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We need RSVPs to make sure we have enough people to warrant splashing the boats.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 10:36:23 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://reidmclaughlin.github.io/eyctr/first-post.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://reidmclaughlin.github.io/eyctr/first-post.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>practice</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
